<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Patches on Daylight Basement Studio LLC</title>
    <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/patch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Patches on Daylight Basement Studio LLC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>daylightbasementgames@gmail.com (dbstudio)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>daylightbasementgames@gmail.com (dbstudio)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:42:16 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://daylightbasementstudio.com/patch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1.0.3-Alpha</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/patch/1-0-3-alpha/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>daylightbasementgames@gmail.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/patch/1-0-3-alpha/</guid>
      <description>UI  Changes to some color profile Warning added to the settings screen Added build number to HUD  Weapons and Items  Chests can now be opened from the top  Enemies  Enemies with pistols and glueguns will fire sooner at the player Enemies with pistols and glueguns have a slightly higher rate of fire  Nav  Stores have less chance to spawn Added some props to dungeon rooms New room added Light changes to rooms Fixed a nav bug that would sometimes result in an empty nav screen after defeating a boss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.0.2-Alpha</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/patch/1-0-2-alpha/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>daylightbasementgames@gmail.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/patch/1-0-2-alpha/</guid>
      <description>Weapons and Items  Fixed issue where ammo was not acquired from store purchases  Misc  Fixed issue where end game would occur prematurely  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.0.1-Alpha</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/patch/1-0-1-alpha/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>daylightbasementgames@gmail.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/patch/1-0-1-alpha/</guid>
      <description>Known Issues  Keyboard and mouse can only be used if the controller is unplugged. If controller is plugged in, it takes priority Hot swapping controller/keyboard will probably not work. We have only tested an xbox controller Some players may experience lower than expected framerate. There are known things we can improve and hope to fix them soon. We&amp;rsquo;ve tested on a GTX 970 and that seems fine. There is no quit button, so alt-tab or alt+F4 to close the game game only supports 16:10 and 16:9 resolutions  UI Overall  Improved look of health bars Holster added back to the player hud Improved minimap look Updated a lot of music Fixed screen effects in menu when loading in the the game for the first time Added a notification for when the player runs out of Radar Jam Fixed travel events Player can no longer re-board visited nodes  Weapons and Items Overall  Fixed a bug around weapons being duplicated with a controller  Calamities  Now reset upon death  Pro͞oves  Reduced cost of all Pro͞oves to 1  RunTime  Pro͞oves granted within a given run are now called RunTimes Now reset upon death (Pro͞oves gained still carry over from run to run)  Radar Jam  Reduced the amount of starting radarjam from 250 to 150 Reduced the amount picked up from 100 to 50  PPSH41  Increased reserved ammo amount from 100 to 850 Reduced the amount of light flashing when shooting  TP82  Increased per bullet damage from 2 to 3  Shotgun  Increased per bullet damage from 4 to 5  Plasma Gun  Increased reserved ammo from 50 to 250  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
