<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Daylight Basement Studio LLC</title>
    <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Daylight Basement Studio LLC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 00:42:16 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://daylightbasementstudio.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Early Access Release Date</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/earlyaccessrelease/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/earlyaccessrelease/</guid>
      <description>RBA CLAWING TO STEAM EARLY ACCESS. JULY 27TH
We are so excited to finally announce the release date of RBA with a new Trailer! Let us know what you think of the new vid. Please share it with your friends!
Thank you for everyone who has followed Beary along this journey. As a small indie studio each and everyone&amp;rsquo;s support means so much to us.
Rightfully, 🐻</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BostonFig 2023</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/bostonfig2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/bostonfig2023/</guid>
      <description>We are excited we were accepted into the BostonFig online showcase! Come visit our virtual booth May 20th, 2023. Visit BostonFIG for more information.
Rightfully, 🐻</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create and host a website on the cheap</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/howtowebsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/howtowebsite/</guid>
      <description>A guide for gamedevs to create professional looking website that are highly customizable and can be easily scaled out for features.
Oh hey, you can look at ours as an example
TLDR The Problem Many website builders, while easy to build, are financially costly. But building a website from scratch has a high effort cost.
Solution Use a static website generator like Hugo hosted on GitHub Pages for a no financial and low effort cost website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Come play a demo at Mill5</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/mill5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/mill5/</guid>
      <description>Friends in the New England area! We will be attending a comic con at the beautiful Mill5 in Lowell MA. 🧵
Come visit us and play an updated RBA demo and get some swag 😎. Be sure to check out the other sweet vendors and artists. ❤️
RSVP on Facebook: https://fb.me/e/4jmaPIxvV 📅
Rightfully, 🐻</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.0.5-Alpha</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/patch/1-0-5-alpha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/patch/1-0-5-alpha/</guid>
      <description>UI Fixed one of the issues that could cause a bug where Beary would spawn outside a room (Thanks Austin of Jolly Crouton!) Fixed a bug where the nav screen would crash after death (Thanks DangerousFsh!) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.0.4-Alpha</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/patch/1-0-4-alpha/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/patch/1-0-4-alpha/</guid>
      <description>UI Reduced some of the gun shooting flashes Pressing esc now allows the player to quit or return to the title screen Smoother camera movement with a controller (Thanks for the feedback @adli_hm 📝) Fixed bugs around being able to drop weapons with a controller. These bugs were likely the cause of another bug that would result in the player not being able to shoot (Thanks to Metal Bat for reporting this &amp;lt;3) Added resource definitions to the game info screen (next to the settings) Weapons and Items Boxes Fixed a bug where a particular room would drop an unlimited amount of Plu (Thank you @ParkAttack for finding this one) TP82 Increased mag size from 3 to 4 Increased rate of fire Increased ammo pickup from 50 to 96 Nav Fixed a bug where some rooms only had a single enemy spawn point </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.0.3-Alpha</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/patch/1-0-3-alpha/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/patch/1-0-3-alpha/</guid>
      <description>UI Changes to some color profile Warning added to the settings screen Added build number to HUD Weapons and Items Chests can now be opened from the top Enemies Enemies with pistols and glueguns will fire sooner at the player Enemies with pistols and glueguns have a slightly higher rate of fire Nav Stores have less chance to spawn Added some props to dungeon rooms New room added Light changes to rooms Fixed a nav bug that would sometimes result in an empty nav screen after defeating a boss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.0.2-Alpha</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/patch/1-0-2-alpha/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/patch/1-0-2-alpha/</guid>
      <description>Weapons and Items Fixed issue where ammo was not acquired from store purchases Misc Fixed issue where end game would occur prematurely </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.0.1-Alpha</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/patch/1-0-1-alpha/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/patch/1-0-1-alpha/</guid>
      <description>Known Issues Keyboard and mouse can only be used if the controller is unplugged. If controller is plugged in, it takes priority Hot swapping controller/keyboard will probably not work. We have only tested an xbox controller Some players may experience lower than expected framerate. There are known things we can improve and hope to fix them soon. We&amp;rsquo;ve tested on a GTX 970 and that seems fine. There is no quit button, so alt-tab or alt+F4 to close the game game only supports 16:10 and 16:9 resolutions UI Overall Improved look of health bars Holster added back to the player hud Improved minimap look Updated a lot of music Fixed screen effects in menu when loading in the the game for the first time Added a notification for when the player runs out of Radar Jam Fixed travel events Player can no longer re-board visited nodes Weapons and Items Overall Fixed a bug around weapons being duplicated with a controller Calamities Now reset upon death Pro͞oves Reduced cost of all Pro͞oves to 1 RunTime Pro͞oves granted within a given run are now called RunTimes Now reset upon death (Pro͞oves gained still carry over from run to run) Radar Jam Reduced the amount of starting radarjam from 250 to 150 Reduced the amount picked up from 100 to 50 PPSH41 Increased reserved ammo amount from 100 to 850 Reduced the amount of light flashing when shooting TP82 Increased per bullet damage from 2 to 3 Shotgun Increased per bullet damage from 4 to 5 Plasma Gun Increased reserved ammo from 50 to 250 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.0.1-Alpha</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/updates/1-0-1-alpha/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/updates/1-0-1-alpha/</guid>
      <description>Known Issues Keyboard and mouse can only be used if the controller is unplugged. If controller is plugged in, it takes priority Hot swapping controller/keyboard will probably not work. We have only tested an Xbox controller Framerate isn&amp;rsquo;t great. We are doing some things not as optimally as we should be, we&amp;rsquo;ve tested on gtx 970 and that seems to play fine. We should have a fix for this soon There is no quit button, so alt-tab or alt+F4 to close the game game only supports 16:10 and 16:9 resolutions UI Overall Improved look of health bars Holster added back to the player hud Improved minimap look Updated a lot of music Fixed screen affects in menu when loading in the the game for the first time Added a notification for when the player runs out of Radar Jam Fixed travel events Player can no longer re-board visited nodes Weapons and Items Overall Fixed a bug around weapons being duplicated with a controller Calamities Now reset upon death Pro͞oves Reduced cost of all Pro͞oves to 1 RunTime Pro͞oves granted within a given run are now called RunTimes Now reset upon death (Pro͞oves gained still carry over from run to run) Radar Jam Reduced the amount of starting radarjam from 250 to 150 Reduced the amount picked up from 100 to 50 PPSH41 Increased reserved ammo amount from 100 to 850 Reduced the amount of light flashing when shooting TP82 Increased per bullet damage from 2 to 3 Shotgun Increased per bullet damage from 4 to 5 Plasma Gun Increased reserved ammo from 50 to 250 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Playtesting Soon</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/open-playtesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/open-playtesting/</guid>
      <description>Thank you all that signed up for RBA open playtesting &amp;lt;3! The amount of players that signed up for playtesting is far more than we initially expected. We are excited to announce that we will begin letting in players within the following week or two. We will continue to let more and more players in as time progresses. We want to make sure there are not any game breaking bugs before mass open playtesting (trust me there are plenty of non game breaking bugs at the moment :D).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Trailer</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/playtesting-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/playtesting-copy/</guid>
      <description>New trailer, just in time for PAX East!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steam Page</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/steampage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/steampage/</guid>
      <description>RBA is now on steam! Be sure to wishlist. Keep an eye out for open play testing sign up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be My Valentine</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/valentines/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/valentines/</guid>
      <description>Share the love! Send these digital valentines to friends and family!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pax East 2022</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/paxeast/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/paxeast/</guid>
      <description>Exciting news! The RBA team will be at Pax East 2022. Come stop by the booth to play a demo of Rightfully, Beary Arms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Testing</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/playtesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/playtesting/</guid>
      <description>Playtesting montage video:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking Into Doors</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/walkingintodoors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 22:09:46 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/walkingintodoors/</guid>
      <description>So we just had our first playtest. Watching others play our game was a lot more fun than I anticipated. We also gain a lot more insight into our own assumptions and understanding of our game.
One hilarious design flaw we discovered: player&amp;rsquo;s have trouble walking through doors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Progression of Colors</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/progression-of-colors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 21:31:59 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/posts/progression-of-colors/</guid>
      <description>I find it hard to consider myself an artist. I&amp;rsquo;ve always been drawn to coding and building before what I consider traditional art. I&amp;rsquo;ve always had an interest in art, but never thought I was any good. I find, generally, that my art practices mimic my coding practices: I often start with abstract ideas then slowly progress to a well defined final product. I enjoy demonstrating that some idea has value: that a single idea might house value without investing an overbearing amount of resources to demonstrate said value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Chris and Mike like games.
April likes people.
Press? Presskit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rightfully, Beary Arms</title>
      <link>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/games/rightfullybearyarms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>games@daylightbasementstudio.com (dbstudio)</author>
      <guid>https://daylightbasementstudio.com/games/rightfullybearyarms/</guid>
      <description>Rightfully, Beary Arms is a bullet hell roguelite that is about much more than collecting loot, dying and losing everything, then repeating. Carefully choose enemy upgrades against your own, then plan your dungeon crawl tactfully to gun through unique factions of enemies, strategically preserving loot after death.
Video not supportedBeary likes to fight. His arsenal is vast but displaced throughout the galaxy. Collect and use powerful weapons, each with their own unique characteristics and learning curves.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
